Omoyokan Moses Adenomor

A passionate and dedicated Web Developer

Benin City adebomor@gmail.com +2349060385985

Hi, I am a passionate and dedicated developer with good experience designing Webapps, crossplatform Apps, utilizing varieties of Software Technologies which include Vuejs, Nuxt, Django, JQuery, Tailwindcss, Scss, Git

I have experience working remotely building meaningful and productive software with also the ability to work with minimal supervision as I have the zeal to tackle any problems I might encounter independently to achieve the desired result.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Frontend Developer Freelancer

Blaqdevs - Remote December 2018 to Present

Freelancer

Intern

University of Benin ICTU, - Benin City August 2019 to February 2020

Front end developer intern for a period of 6 months

Education

B.Sc in Industrial Mathematics

University Of Benin - Benin City October 2016 to August 2021

Skills

- Vuejs
- Quasar
- Java Script
- HTML5
- CSS3

- Wordpress
- Tailwind
- Bootstrap

Links

http://linkedin.com/in/omoyokan-moses-adenomor-97445b156

https://github.com/BlaqDevs

Additional Information

English